MANFRED BARABARA

Web developer & Graphic designer

Email: manfredbarabara@gmail.com

Phone: +254 715360483

Profile summary

I'm a versatile professional with in-depth knowledge and great skills primarily in front end web development, UI/UX design and graphic design. My great proficiency level in HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Git, Adobe Creative Suite (Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign and Adobe XD) enable me to perform and deliver efficiently and effectively in all of the above mentioned fields due to my flexibility and experience hence making me a top notch front end developer as well as a graphic designer. With all these qualities, I create data driven solutions that elevate human experiences.

Education background

Sept 2014 - Dec 2018,

Meru university of science and technology

Bachelor of science in computer science

Feb 2010 - Nov 2013,

Allidina visram high school

Kenya certificate of secondary education

Competencies and skills

- HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, GIT, python, Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign and Adobe XD.
- UI/UX design (wire framing & high fidelity mock-ups)
- Graphic design
- Branding
- Version control

Job experience

Feb 2023 - current,

Ministry of education (DLP INTERN)

Working as an ICT officer to facilitate Digital Literacy Program in public primary schools.

Oct 2018 - Dec 2018,

Kenya school of government, Mombasa campus

Attachment under ICT department

Jul 2017 - sept 2017,

Kenya Ports Authority

Attachment under ICT department

Referees

Mrs. Mary Mwadulo

Meru university of science and technology

Lecturer

Tel +254 724789102

Mr. Victor Nyongesa

Likoni furniture (manager)

Mentor

Tel +254 724913888